So we're back on car.py file and let's see how we
下面 我们回到 car.py 文件 让我们看看如何
can actually modify this car object and add a color variable.
修改这个汽车对象并添加一个颜色变量
Inside our class code,
在我们的类代码中
we can see that there's a default color for our car.
我们可以看到 汽车有一个默认颜色
Red, represented by the character r. How do you think we might customize this?
红色 由字符 r 表示 你觉得我们应该如何定制这个颜色？
Well, just like with our state variables in our world,
那么就像这个世界中的状态变量的定制一样
we can pass it in in our initialization parameters.
我们可以在初始化参数中导入颜色
To do this in the usual way,
通常情况下 要这样做
we just add an extra parameter to our init function.
我们只需要在 init 函数添加一个额外的参数
I'll call this parameter, color.
我会调用颜色这个参数
I can also specify a default value for color equal to red,
我也可以指定颜色的默认值为红色
equal to the character,
等于这个字符
r. This color equals r means that if and only
r 该颜色等于 r 就意味着在且仅在以下条件
if a person does not specify a color parameter when a car object is created,
即在创建汽车对象时没有指定颜色参数时
it will, by default, be red.
默认情况下 它将是红色的
None of our other variables have a default value.
其他变量都没有默认值
Then we also have to change this one other line of code.
然后我们还必须改变另一行代码
And instead of saying self.color equals r,
这里 self.color 不等于 r
we say self.color equals color,
而是等于颜色
and this is the passed in variable here.
这就是我们之前在这里使用的变量
So now, our init function initializes the state of our car,
所以现在 我们的 init 函数初始化了车的状态
gives our car a 2D world to traverse,
给了这台车一个可以穿行的 2D 世界
and it specifies the color of the car.
并指定了车的颜色
All that's left to do is to test this out in executable code,
剩下的一切就是用可执行代码来测试
so let's go into a new notebook.
所以让我们进入一个新的 notebook
Here are our usual import statements where we import our car class file.
这是我们通常的导入声明 在此导入我们的汽车类文件
Next, I'll create car objects.
接下来 我将创建汽车对象
Here, I'm defining the initial parameters and
在这里 我定义了初始参数
I'm creating carla in the same way as I usually do.
我正在按照通常的方式创建 carla
And then I'll define some new initial parameters and I'll create a new car object.
然后 我将定义一些新的初始参数 创建一个新的汽车对象
This time, I'll name the car, jeannette.
这一次 我会把车命名为 jeannette
As you can see, I'm passing in our initial state variables, position2, and velocity2.
你可以看到 我正在输入初始状态变量 position2 和 velocity2
I'm passing in the same world and I'm also passing in
我在导入同一个世界 我还在导入
a color and specifying that jeannette has a yellow color with the character,
颜色并指定 jeannette 为黄色 具体做法是采用字符
y, as our last passed In variable.
y 表示 作为我们最后一次导入的变量
And order is important here,
顺序在这里很重要
this should match the order in our car class file.
应该符合我们汽车类文件中的顺序
So now, I should have two cars,
现在我应该有两辆车
carla and jeannette, and I'll run this cell of the notebook.
carla 和 jeannette 我会运行 notebook 的这个单元格
Now, if you get an error at this step,
现在 如果在此步骤中出现错误
make sure you saved your car class file after you've changed it and
请确保你在更改了的汽车类文件后已经保存
restart your kernel by clicking Kernel and Restart &amp; Clear Output.
通过单击 Kernel 然后点击 Restart &amp; Clear Output 重新启动 Kernel
So, since I didn't get any errors,
现在 既然没有任何错误
my next step will be to write some move code for both of these cars.
我的下一步将是为这两辆车写一些移动代码
And this is just for fun and visualization.
这很有趣 只是为了可视化
First, I'm going to move carla,
首先 我将移动 carla
telling carla to move and turn left and move again,
告诉 carla 移动 并左转 然后再移动
and then I'm going to display carla's world.
然后我要显示 carla 的世界
We can see carla's movement,
我们可以看到 carla 的移动
moving forward then left and looping around the world,
向前移动 然后向左并环绕世界
and we see that carla is red.
我们看到 carla 是红色的
Red is the default color since we didn't specify
红色是默认颜色 因为我们在创建时没有指定
a color when we created carla. Let's scroll back down.
一种颜色 让我们向下滚动
Next, I'm going to move jeannette,
接下来 我将移动 jeannette
turn left and moving and turning left and moving some more,
左转 然后移动 然后左转 然后再移动一点
and I'll display jeannette's world.
我会显示 jeannette 的世界
We can see that jeanette started off at a different point
我们可以看到 jeanette 的开始角度不同
and sort of looped around creating a different path.
并创建了不同的路径进行循环移动
And we see that jeannette is yellow,
我们看到 jeannette 是黄色的
including the path so this is pretty cool.
包括路径也是黄色的 这非常酷
Adding more variables like a car color can be just a couple of lines of code.
添加汽车颜色等更多变量 只需要几行代码
This is also the case with functions.
函数也一样
You can have their definitions to a class and then be able to access them.
你可以将它们的定义应用于类 然后就能访问它们了